Huanyu Wang

WEB DEVELOPER

huanyuw01@gmail.com 604-789-3286 Portfolio linkedin.com/in/huanyu-wang/ github.com/hnslyswhy

PROFILE

With the blended experience of education and aviation, I'm passionate about solving problems and always pay close attention to details and communication. Inspired by Women in Tech, and driven by the desire to bridge the disconnection between aviation learners and aviation training providers, I started my coding journey to build useful applications in service of others.

SKILLS

Fluent: React.js, Node.js, Express.js, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS/SASS, Rest APIs, Git, Document Object Model(DOM) APIs

Proficient: Mongodb, User Authentication, OAuth, Object Store / Blobstore, JWT

Some Experience: Firebase, MySQL, Jest, Enzyme, Material UI, Python

PROJECTS

4Forces | Full stack | Aviation Social and Educational App

React.js, Web API, Axios, Sass, Node.js, Express.js, Helmet, Morgan, Mongodb, Object Store(Digital Ocean)

4Goods | Full stack | Social Good App | Black Wing Hacks 2022

React.js, Google Map API, Sass, Node.js, Express.js, JTW Token, Mongodb, Cloudinary

Instock | Full stack | Warehouse Management App | Group Project

React.js, Node.js, Express.js, Axios, Sass

Launcheruu | Full stack | Project Countdown Appy

React.js, Node.js, Express.js, Axios, Sass

EDUCATION

BrainStation | Diploma, Web Development

OCT 2021 - FEB 2022, VANCOUVER, CANADA

University of British Columbia | Master of Educational Technology

SEP 2021 - PRESENT, VANCOUVER, CANADA

Liaoning Normal University | Bachelor of Arts in English Education

SEP 2009 - 2013, DALIAN, CHINA, GPA:3.8

EXPERIENCE

Project Manager | Langley Flying School

2018 - 2021, LANGLEY, BC, CANADA

- Successfully launched a university credit transfer program by applying skills in planning, documentation, and organization;
- Gained business opportunities through signing ten admission partners and setting-up pilot pathways for graduates with two general aviation companies.

Pilot | Ameriflight

2016 - 2017, SEATTLE, WA, USA

• Ensured the safety and punctuality of daily cargo flights as a first officer by strictly following the flight operation manual.

English Teacher | New Oriental School

2013 - 2014, LUOYANG, HENAN, CHINA

• Enhanced students' English grammar knowledge and writing skills by using self-developed teaching plans, materials, and exams.